Nature Has Evolved
Extinction is a thriller, adventure film directed by Adam Spinks.
Deep in the Amazon jungle a group of scientists are on a dangerous mission.
When their guide suddenly abandons them, they find
themselves in a savage and hostile environment.
However, things turn deadly when they find they are in the middle of a hunting
ground for a pack of prehistoric predators long thought extinct.
Professor John Howson, played by Ben Loyd-Holmes.
Michelle, played by Sarah Mac.
Rob, played by Neil Newbon.
James, played by Daniel Caren.
Lisa, played by Emma Lillie Lees.
Tim, played by Simon Burbage.
Extinction is a 2018 American science fiction action film directed by
Ben Young and written by Spenser Cohen and Brad Kane.
The film is about a father who has a recurring dream/vision about the loss of
his family while witnessing an evil force bent on destruction.
The film stars Michael Peña, Lizzy Caplan, Mike Colter, Lilly
Aspell, Emma Booth, Israel Broussard, and Lex Shrapnel.
Extinction was filmed over 40 days in Belgrade,
Serbia, on a budget of $20 million.
It had originally been scheduled for a theatrical release on January 26, 2018,
by Universal Pictures, but was pulled from the release schedule.
The film was acquired from Universal by Netflix,
which released it on July 27, 2018.
It received negative reviews, with criticism for its confused and
weak storyline, character development and pacing.
The film explores themes of monster, amazon rainforest,
jungle, prehistory, prehistoric creature.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.